(this.webpackJsonpyopardy=this.webpackJsonpyopardy||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('[{"name":"JS","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"When this is used, a variable can not be reassigned.","answer":"const"},{"value":200,"question":"The context in which values are visible or can be referenced.","answer":"scope"},{"value":300,"question":"The combination of a function with reference to its lexical environment.","answer":"Closure"},{"value":400,"question":"The three most common ways to handle asynchronous operations in JavaScript.","answer":"Callbacks, Promises, async/await"},{"value":500,"question":"This is JavaScript\'s inheritance model.","answer":"The prototype chain"}]},{"name":"CS","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"The repetition of a sequence of computer instructions a specified number of times or until a condition is met.","answer":"loop"},{"value":200,"question":"Time required for a function to execute based on its input size.","answer":"Big O notation"},{"value":300,"question":"Programming technique involving the use of a procedure, subroutine, function, or algorithm that calls itself one or more times until a specified condition is met.","answer":"Recursion"},{"value":400,"question":"In this data structure, for any given node C, if P is a parent node of C, then the key (the value) of P is greater than or equal to the key of C.","answer":"Heap"},{"value":500,"question":"A form of automatic memory management which reclaims memory occupied by objects that are no longer in use by the program.","answer":"Garbage collection"}]},{"name":"BACKEND","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"The most popular Node framework, allowing us to write handlers for requests with different HTTP verbs at different URL paths.","answer":"Express"},{"value":200,"question":"Computer program or a device that provides functionality for other programs or devices, called \\"clients\\".","answer":"Server"},{"value":300,"question":"A small piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user\'s computer by the user\'s web browser while the user is browsing.","answer":"Cookie"},{"value":400,"question":"A keyword in SQL that allows you to rename a column or table using an alias.","answer":"AS"},{"value":500,"question":"Refers to the management of incremental, reversible changes and version control for relational database schemas.","answer":"Schema migration"}]},{"name":"FRONTEND","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"The API to a webpage, allowing programs to read and manipulate the page content, structure, and styles.","answer":"DOM"},{"value":200,"question":"Describes all HTML elements, and includes content, padding, border and margin.","answer":"The CSS box model"},{"value":300,"question":"HTML5 convention via which HTML elements clearly describe their meaning to both the browser and the developer, as well as providing enhanced accessibility.","answer":"Semantic elements"},{"value":400,"question":"A React hook which serves the same purpose as componentDidMount, componentDidUpdate, and componentWillUnmount did in React classes, but unified into a single API.","answer":"useEffect"},{"value":500,"question":"A JavaScript API for rendering interactive 2D and 3D graphics within any compatible web browser without the use of plug-ins.","answer":"WebGL"}]},{"name":"CI/CD","questions":[{"value":100,"question":"It advocates adaptive planning, evolutionary development, early delivery, and continual improvement, and it encourages rapid and flexible response to change.","answer":"Agile"},{"value":200,"question":"A software development practice where members of a team combine their work frequently.","answer":"Continuous Integration"},{"value":300,"question":"Design philosophy stating that rather than making users work around the product, the product should work around the user.","answer":"User Centered Design"},{"value":400,"question":"An approach to building new businesses based on the belief that entrepreneurs must investigate, experiment, test and iterate as they develop products.","answer":"Lean Startup"},{"value":500,"question":"Used to help a product manager (and others in the organization involved with the product\'s development) understand key traits, behaviors, goals, responsibilities, and needs of a specific type of user.","answer":"Persona"}]}]')},15:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(34)},20:function(e,t,n){},34:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),s=n.n(a),r=n(9),o=n.n(r),i=(n(20),function(){return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"header"},"\ud83c\udf4d y o p a r d y")}),c=n(4),u=n(10),l=Object(u.a)((function(e,t){return{team:"t1",setTeam:function(t){return e({team:t})},selected:"",setSelected:function(t){e({selected:t})},answered:[],setAnswered:function(t){localStorage.setItem("answered",JSON.stringify(t)),e({answered:t})},score:{t1:0,t2:0,t3:0},setScore:function(t){localStorage.setItem("score",JSON.stringify(t));var n={score:t,lastUpdated:(new Date).toString()};e({scoreLastUpdated:n}),e({score:t})},scoreLastUpdated:{score:{t1:0,t2:0,t3:0},lastUpdated:(new Date).toString()},setScoreLastUpdated:function(t){return e({scoreLastUpdated:t})},reset:function(){var t={t1:0,t2:0,t3:0};localStorage.setItem("score",JSON.stringify(t)),localStorage.setItem("answered",JSON.stringify()),e({answered:[]}),e({score:t})}}})),m=Object(c.a)(l,1)[0],d=Object(a.memo)((function(e){var t=e.value,n=e.question,r=m((function(e){return e.setSelected})),o=m((function(e){return e.answered}));Object(a.useEffect)((function(){console.log(o,n)}));var i=Object(a.useCallback)((function(){r(n)}),[r,n]);return s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement("div",{onClick:i,className:"question"},o.includes(n.question)?"\ud83e\udd51":t))})),f=n(2),p=n.n(f),v=function(e){var t=e.name,n=e.questions;return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"column"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"column-header"},t),n.map((function(e){return s.a.createElement(d,{qid:e.id,key:p.a.generate(),value:e.value,question:e,answers:e.answers})})))},h=n(11),w=function(){return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"questions"},h.map((function(e){return s.a.createElement(v,{key:p.a.generate(),name:e.name,questions:e.questions})})))},b=Object(a.memo)((function(){var e=m((function(e){return e.setTeam})),t=m((function(e){return e.team})),n=m((function(e){return e.score})),r=Object(a.useCallback)((function(t){e(t)}),[e]);return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"teams"},s.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(e){r(e.target.id)},className:"team ".concat("t1"===t&&"team-selected"),id:"t1"},"TEAM 1 ","t1"===t?"\ud83d\udd2e":"\ud83d\udc85\ud83c\udffc",s.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-display"},n.t1)),s.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(e){r(e.target.id)},className:"team ".concat("t2"===t&&"team-selected"),id:"t2"},"TEAM 2 ","t2"===t?"\ud83d\udd2e":"\ud83d\udc85\ud83c\udffc",s.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-display"},n.t2)),s.a.createElement("div",{onClick:function(e){r(e.target.id)},className:"team ".concat("t3"===t&&"team-selected"),id:"t3"},"TEAM 3 ","t3"===t?"\ud83d\udd2e":"\ud83d\udc85\ud83c\udffc",s.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-display"},n.t3)))})),g=n(14),E=n(3),q=n(12),y=n(5),S=n.n(y),N=function(e){var t=m((function(e){return e.selected})),n=m((function(e){return e.setSelected})),r=m((function(e){return e.score})),o=m((function(e){return e.setScore})),i=m((function(e){return e.team})),u=Object(a.useState)(!1),l=Object(c.a)(u,2),d=l[0],f=l[1],p=m((function(e){return e.answered})),v=m((function(e){return e.setAnswered})),h=function(){n(null),f(!d)};return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-modal"},s.a.createElement(S.a,{bottom:!0},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-modal-question"},t.question)),d?s.a.createElement(S.a,{bottom:!0},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-modal-answer"},t.answer.toUpperCase())):s.a.createElement("button",{className:"show-answer-button",onClick:function(){f(!d),v([].concat(Object(g.a)(p),[t.question]))}},"SHOW ANSWER"),d&&s.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-buttons"},s.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){o(Object(q.a)({},r,Object(E.a)({},i,r[i]+t.value))),h()},className:"hell-yeah-button"},"HELL YEAH!"," ",s.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"red cross"},"\u2705")),s.a.createElement("button",{onClick:h,className:"close-modal-button"},d?"NOPE":"CLOSE"," ",s.a.createElement("span",{role:"img","aria-label":"red cross"},"\u274c"))))},C=n(13),O=n.n(C);var k=function(){var e=m((function(e){return e.setScore})),t=m((function(e){return e.setAnswered})),n=m((function(e){return e.reset})),r=m((function(e){return e.selected})),o=m((function(e){return e.scoreLastUpdated})),c=Object(a.useCallback)((function(){var t=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("score"));t&&e(t)}),[e]),u=Object(a.useCallback)((function(){var e=JSON.parse(localStorage.getItem("answered"));e&&t(e)}),[t]);return Object(a.useEffect)((function(){c(),u()}),[c,u]),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},s.a.createElement(i,null),s.a.createElement(w,null),s.a.createElement(b,null),r&&s.a.createElement(N,null),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-last-updated"},"SCORE LAST UPDATED:"," ",O()(o.lastUpdated).format("MMMM Do YYYY, h:mm:ss a").toUpperCase()),s.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){n()},className:"reset-score-button"},"RESET SCORE"))};o.a.render(s.a.createElement(k,null),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[15,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2439da13.chunk.js.map